question_data = [{"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The retail disc of Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater 5 only comes with the tutorial.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In 1993 Swedish car manufacturer Saab experimented with replacing the steering wheel with a joystick in a Saab 9000.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "This is the correct spelling of &quot;Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The Kingdom of Prussia briefly held land in Estonia.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Joseph Stalin&#039;s real name was Ioseb Bessarionis dze Dzugashvili.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Comics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In the comic book &quot;Archie&quot;, Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In the game &quot;Melty Blood Actress Again Current Code&quot;, you can enter Blood Heat mode in Half Moon style.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The first &quot;Metal Gear&quot; game was released for the PlayStation 1.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The binary number &quot;101001101&quot; is equivalent to the Decimal number &quot;334&quot;", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "&quot;Number 16 Bus Shelter&quot; was a child&#039;s name that was approved by the New Zealand government.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In &quot;Portal 2&quot;, Cave Johnson started out Aperture Science as a shower curtain company.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The fourth funnel of the RMS Titanic was fake designed to make the ship look more powerful and symmetrical.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In Undertale, having a &quot;Fun Value&quot; set to 56-57 will play the &quot;Wrong Number Song Call&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Rannamaari was a sea demon that haunted the people of the Maldives and had to be appeased monthly with the sacrifice of a virgin girl.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "DHCP stands for Dynamic Host Configuration Port.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Throughout the entirety of &quot;Dragon Ball Z&quot;, Goku only kills two characters: a miniboss named Yakon and Kid Buu.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The song &quot;Mystery Train&quot; was released by artist &quot;Little Junior&#039;s Blue Flames&quot; in 1953.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "&quot;Cube&quot;, &quot;Cube 2: Hypercube&quot; and &quot;Cube Zero&quot; were directed by the same person.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In Scandinavian languages, the letter &Aring; means river.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Switzerland has four national languages, English being one of them.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The band STRFKR was also briefly known as Pyramiddd.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The chemical element Lithium is named after the country of Lithuania.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The USS Missouri (BB-63) last served in the Korean War.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Nazi Germany surrendered on Harry Truman&#039;s birthday while he was president.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Druid is a mage class in &quot;Log Horizon&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The Klingon home planet is Qo&#039;noS.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The value of one Calorie is different than the value of one calorie.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "During the Winter War, the amount of Soviet Union soliders that died or went missing was five times more than Finland&#039;s.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Stagecoach owned &quot;South West Trains&quot; before losing the rights to FirstGroup and MTR in March of 2017.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The weapon Clint Eastwood uses in &quot;Dirty Harry&quot; was a .44 Automag.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "George Clinton, Vice President of the United States (1805-1812), is an ancestor of President Bill Clinton.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Pete Townshend&#039;s solo album, &quot;White City: A Novel&quot;, is set in the metropolitan area of Chicago.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, Peke is considered a female robot.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Spoon theory is a theory, utilizing &quot;Spoons&quot; as a metaphor for energy they can use in a day.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The song Scatman&#039;s World was released after Scatman (Ski-Ba-Bop-Ba-Dop-Bop).", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In the &quot;Kagerou Daze&quot; series, Shintaro Kisaragi is prominently shown with the color red.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Janus was the Roman god of doorways and passageways.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The character Plum from &quot;No Game No Life&quot; is a girl.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The video game &quot;Fuel&quot; has an open world that is 5,560 square miles?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In &quot;Minecraft&quot;, gold tools are faster than diamond tools.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Art", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The Statue of Liberty&#039;s official name is &ldquo;Liberty Enlightening the World&rdquo;.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The man that shot Alexander Hamilton was named Aaron Burr.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Only one country in the world starts with the letter Q.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "YouTube personality Jenna Marbles served as an executive producer of the film Maximum Ride (2016).", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The T-Mobile Sidekick smartphone is a re-branded version of the Danger Hiptop.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The Paradox Interactive game &quot;Stellaris&quot; was released in 2016.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The protagonist in &quot;Humanity Has Declined&quot; has no discernable name and is simply referred to as &#039;I&#039; for most of the series.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Musicals & Theatres", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The protagonist&#039;s names in &#039;Who&#039;s Afraid of Virginia Woolf&#039;, George and Martha, were derived from George Washington and his wife.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In The Witcher 3, the Zoltan Chivay Gwent card can be found under the Hanged Man&#039;s Tree.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
